Hello, little fella.
你好  小伙子
Heh heh heh! Beauty, isn't he?
呵呵呵  很漂亮  是不是
I found that guy struggling for life......out on the reef, and I saved him.
我在暗礁那里发现了这个小家伙 他正在拼命挣扎  于是我救了他
So, has that Novocaine kicked in yet?
那么  麻醉剂已经生效了吗
I think so. We're ready to roll.
我认为是的  我们可以开始了
Bubbles!Bubbles!
泡泡 泡泡
My bubbles.
我的泡泡
He likes bubbles.
他喜欢泡泡
Aah! Ohh! No! Uhh!
啊  喔  不  啊
-Bonjour. -Aah!
-你好  -啊
Slow down, little fella. There's nothing to worry about.
慢点  小家伙  没有什么可以担心的
-Oh he's scared to death. -I want to go home.
-他吓得要死  -我想回家
Do you know where my dad is?
你们知道我爸爸在哪吗
Honey, your dad's probably back at the pet store.
亲爱的  你爸爸可能已经回宠物店了
Pet store?
宠物店
Yeah, you know, like, I'm from Bob's Fish Mart.
是啊  你知道  像是  我是来自鲍勃的鱼类超市
-Pet Palace. -Fish-O-Rama.
-宠物皇宫  -来自鱼店
-Mail order. -Ebay.
-邮购  -EBay
-So, which one is it? -I'm from the ocean.
-那么  你是哪来的  -我从海里来
Ah, the ocean. The ocean?
啊  大海  大海
He hasn't been decontaminated. Jacques!
他还没有经过消毒  虾虾
-Oui. -Clean him!
-是  -给他清洗一下
Oui.
是
-Ocean. -Ooh, la mer. Bon.
-大海里来的  -喔  大海里来的  好的
Voila. He is clean.
这样就行了  他干净了